Welcome to Manulife Vitality Stories!
Once upon a time, Jean got a new Apple Watch
and here’s the twist:
she got it at a huge discount thanks to her
Manulife Vitality Plus membership!
The first chapter in Jean’s Apple
Watch story was to order it.
It was easy!
She just logged into her online account,
chose her model and ordered it.
You can also use the app.
In Chapter 2, Jean was kept up to date with ordering and shipping confirmation emails.
Then within eight weeks it was at her door and on her wrist
Next, Chapter 3 showed her the easy on-screen instructions to pair her watch with her iPhone
then connect it to the program.
First, she opened her Manulife Vitality app.
It was her first time connecting the Health app, so a pop-up guided her through the easy process.
If you’re reconnecting the Health app, you won’t see that pop-up.
So, click “Profile,” then “Apps and Devices.” Select “Health app,” then click the “Connect” button.
When your Health app opens, click “Sharing” and then “Apps and Services.”
Select “Manulife Vitality” and then “Turn On All.”
From there, you’ll be ready to get moving and earn Vitality Points
which led Jean to Chapter 4!
When Jean moves – and even sleeps – her watch and the app can record it all, including her steps and heart rate.
And all that can translate to Vitality Points and rewards!
Finally, Chapter 5 is the end – or is it?
Jean’s Apple Watch story truly has no end, because it’s all about moving forward with Manulife Vitality!
Now it’s time to get moving, so you can enjoy your Apple Watch – and Manulife Vitality – as much as Jean does!
Want to check out more Manulife Vitality “how-to” stories?
Click on one of the other videos you see here, then you could live happily ever after!